Previously on the show.
上集說到
The cannon Wolffy accidentally fired hit the weather tree,
灰太狼無意中發射的砲彈 擊中了天氣樹
making it unable to produce weather fruits.
令天氣樹無法再結出天氣果
When the last weather seed was finally found,
好不容易找回最後的一顆天氣種子
Paddi swallowed it.
又被懶羊羊吞下了肚子
What will he and the others do next?
接下來小希他們該如何是好呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Running Paddi."
《奇幻天空島之》
What? Paddi ate the last weather seed?
什麼？ 懶羊羊吃了最後一顆天氣種子？
Look at his head. It has sprouted.
快看看他頭上，都長出樹苗了
There's never been a case of a weather seed growing on a person.
這天氣樹苗長在人身上的例子 從來沒有過啊
Paddi, do you feel anything different?
懶羊羊 你現在有什麼特別的感覺嗎？
I feel dizzy.
暈暈的感覺
Could it be a side effect from the weather seed?
這不會是天氣種子的副作用吧？
No. Based on my years of experience,
不，根據我多年的了解
Paddi is probably just dizzy from hunger.
懶羊羊頭暈應該是肚子餓造成的
Weslie knows me best.
果然還是喜羊羊了解我
Look. He's feeling energized now.
看吧，馬上就有精神了
A bit of pepper will be perfect.
再加點胡椒粉就完美了
Is it finished already?
這麼快就用完了嗎？
Paddi, what's that on your head?
懶羊羊，你頭上這是？
A wind fruit grew on your head!
居然長了個風果
No way.
不是吧？
Who knew Paddi's sneeze would yield a wind fruit?
沒想到懶羊羊打了個噴嚏 就能長出風果
Could we get other fruits if Paddi did something else?
如果讓懶羊羊做其它的事情 不知道會不會也長出其它的果子呢？
Let's give it a try.
不如我們試一試吧
I see. Sweating gives us rain fruit.
原來如此，流汗就可以結出雨果
What if he sweated more?
如果再多出一點汗會怎麼樣呢？
Paddi, keep running. Don't stop.
懶羊羊，繼續跑，不要停
It worked. The more he sweats, the bigger the fruit is.
真的出汗越多果子越大呀
Let me make you a gigantic rain fruit.
讓我來給你們做個超大的雨果
Sorry.
對不起
Snoring gives us thunder fruits.
原來打呼嚕就會結出雷果
We're running low on weather fruits.
現在天氣果的庫存越來越少了
If we don't get more soon, we'll be in big trouble.
要是再沒有天氣果產出麻煩就大了
Yes, more and more orders are on hold.
是啊，訂單積壓得越來越多了
Don't worry, everyone.
大家不用擔心
We have a temporary way of producing weather fruits.
我們已經找到 臨時生產天氣果的辦法了
Leave it to me.
交給我吧
Do your best, Paddi. I'll be with you the whole time.
加油啊，懶羊羊 我會跟你共同進退的
All right, let's begin.
好，我們開始吧
Keep it up, Paddi. Keep going!
加油啊，懶羊羊，加油
This is strange. Where did Weslie go?
奇怪，喜羊羊去哪了？
Why is there a telescope here?
怎麼會有個望遠鏡？
Hope, have you seen Weslie?
小希，妳看見喜羊羊了嗎？
I haven't, not today.
我今天沒有看見他
What was that sound?
剛才那是什麼聲音啊？
What's going on?
怎麼了？
I haven't seen you all day. Have you been sleeping?
整天都見不到你，原來在睡覺
Didn't you say you'd be with me?
不是說共進退的嗎？
I'm doing all the hard work here.
明明是我比較累啊
I'm starving.
好餓啊
Let me buy some food first.
先去買點吃的吧
Weslie, get up. It's time for dinner.
喜羊羊，起床了，吃飯了
Hello.
你好
Let me take your mark energy,
讓我先把你們的印記能量吸走
and turn you into a goat feast.
讓後再把你們做成羊肉大餐
Where's my energy extractor? Where is it?
我的能量提取器呢？放哪了？
Weslie! Weslie, wake up!
喜羊羊…快醒來
So you're awake.
原來你已經醒了
I... I'm not. Look, I'm asleep.
我…並沒有，看，我是睡著的
I wouldn't have caught Weslie so easily if it was not for you.
要不是你，我抓喜羊羊沒那麼順利
Thank you so much, Paddi.
懶羊羊，還真得謝謝你呢
What?
什麼？
Weslie exhausted himself trying to help you.
喜羊羊為了幫你，累成這樣了
Help me?
幫我？
I know you've been busy making weather fruits these days.
我知道這幾天你們忙於生產天氣果
I must catch you all this time.
這回我一定要把你們抓回來
Where is Weslie?
喜羊羊去哪兒了？
Wolffy!
灰太狼
Bye.
再見
Why is there a telescope here?
怎麼會有個望遠鏡？
Here's my chance.
機會來了
You again?
又…是…你
What was that sound?
剛剛是什麼聲音？
Wolffy!
灰太狼
After being tricked so many times, I came prepared this time.
吃了那麼多次虧 這次我可是早有準備的
Are you prepared for this then?
那這個你準備好了嗎？
What's going on?
怎麼了？
Because of my persistence, Weslie is finally exhausted.
在我的不懈努力下 喜羊羊終於被我累倒了
Without Weslie's protection, catching both of you is a piece of cake.
沒了喜羊羊的保護 要捉你們，還不是手到擒來嗎？
I've... I've misunderstood Weslie.
原來…原來我一直誤會了喜羊羊
Do you think it's easy to catch you? Whatever.
你說我抓羊容易嗎？算了
Extracting your energy is more important.
趕緊提取能量才是正事
Let go of Weslie!
你快放開喜羊羊！
Be patient. You're next.
別急，下一個就是你
What should I do? Oh, right!
怎麼辦？對了
That's weird. What is the problem?
奇怪，哪裡出了問題了嗎？
Do you think you can get away?
你以為你能逃跑嗎？
How dare you actually try to run away?
居然真的想自己逃走啊
Stop!
別跑
Paddi has gotten more capable lately.
這懶羊羊最近真的長本事了
How can he run so long without getting tired?
跑了這麼久還那麼有勁啊
These weather fruits don't work on me anymore.
這些天氣果已經對本大王沒用了
Why is it raining so hard?
這雨怎麼這麼大呀？
Don't underestimate the rainstorm fruit, Wolffy.
千萬不能小看暴雨果的威力啊 灰太狼
I won't let you get away, Paddi!
懶羊羊，今天我跟你沒完
You're done.
今天到此為止了
No way.
不是吧？
I will be back!
我一定會回來的
Paddi?
懶羊羊？
You're finally awake, Weslie.
喜羊羊，你終於睡醒了
Why are we here?
我們怎麼會在這啊？
We were captured by Wolffy,
我們剛剛被灰太狼捉走了
but it's all fine now.
不過現在沒事了
No matter what happens, I'll protect you from now on.
以後不論發生任何事情 我都會保護你的
Thank you, Paddi.
謝謝你啊，懶羊羊
Why didn't you tell me about all Wolffy's ambushes?
對了，為什麼灰太狼一直偷襲我 你都不告訴我？
Weslie, I was afraid you'd be scared stiff.
我是怕你看到灰太狼嚇得跑不動啊
What? I'm going home.
什麼嘛，我要回去了
Just kidding. Wait for me.
我開玩笑的啦，等等我
TO BE CONTINUED 2776 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續 距離啟航還剩2776天）